你在做什么  我重新整理过冰箱
What are you doing? I reorganized the fridge, heh.
看  最底下  放肉跟奶制品
See? Uh, bottom shelf, meats and dairy.
中间  放水果蔬菜
Middle shelf, fruits and vegetables.
最上面  放过期食物
And top shelf, expired products.
你吃饱撑着啊  因为我无聊到快抓狂了
Why are you doing this? Because I am bored out of my mind.
我已经去过银行  邮局  干洗店
I've already been to the bank, post office and dry cleaners.
老兄  你做完我一周的工作了
Dude, you just described seven days worth of stuff.
你要把工作分散一点  难道你从来没失业过
Gotta spread it out a little, you know. Haven't you ever been unemployed?
我不是失业  只是进修中（有安息之意）
I am not unemployed. I'm on sabbatical.
少跟我传教  拜托
Hey, don't get religious on me, okay?
你应该练习放轻松
A guy in your position needs to be a little better at relaxing, you know.
不然我们家怎么会有安乐椅啊  过来  坐下
Why do you think we have the comfortable chairs, huh? Here, sit down.
准备好没  仔细看了
Ready? Watch.
然后
And then...
真好
AW, yeah! Huh?
就这样  光坐着  当然不是
So, what? We just sit? Oh, no, no.
不只是坐着  看好了
We're not gonna just sit. Watch.
哈喽  我是钱德宾
Hello. Chandler Bing.
哈喽  宾先生
Hello, Mr. Bing.
我爱你
I love you.
好了  不管你是谁  别再打了
All right, whoever this is, stop calling me.
你已经骚扰我半年了  一点也不好笑
It's been six months! It's not funny!
但是  我爱你
But I love you.
求求你  行行好  别再骚扰我了
Leave me alone! For the love of God, leave me alone!
这只是周三的乐子
And that's Wednesday. Ah!
老友记  第五季  第10集  情比兄妹深
Friends  S05E10  The One With The Inappropriate Sister
主演: 珍妮佛·安妮斯顿
主演: 寇妮·考克斯
主演: 丽莎·库卓
主演: 麦特·勒布兰
主演: 马修·派瑞
主演: 大卫·修蒙
嘿  告诉你们
Hey, you guys. Guess what?
英国人要打来啦
The British are coming'
你的笑话真冷
Oh, you and your ways.
耶诞节快到了  我要负责去募捐
Since it's Christmas, I'm gonna be one of those people collecting donations.
我已经拿到铃铛  过几天就能拿到募捐筒
Yeah. I already have my bell, and later on I get my bucket.
对  我要散播欢乐给大家
Yeah, yeah. I'll be spreading joy to the people.
去年散播的不够多
Last year I spread a little joy, but not enough.
所以今年  一定要让全纽约都感受到
So this year, I'm gonna do the whole city. Heh.
我有个高中同学也跟你一样  她很红
I knew a girl in high school who did that. She was very popular.
菲比  你要去哪里摇铃呢
Uh, so, Pheebs, where are you doing your bell ringing?
我分到梅西百货旁当红的位子
They gave me a great spot right by Macy's.
新人很少能分到这个位子
They never give such a good corner to a rookie...
可是只有我会用25种语言  说圣诞快乐
...but I'm the only one who can say "Merry Christmas" in 25 languages.
我胡编的
I lied.
天啊  丹尼在那边
Oh, my God. Okay, you guys, here's Danny.
你们看
Just watch this.
看见没  还假装对我没兴趣
See? Still pretending he's not interested.
他走过来了  大家装作不认识  忘记他是谁
Okay, he's coming over. Pretend we've forgotten who he is.
你们好  丹尼
Hey, guys. Hey, Danny.
喔  丹尼
Oh, Danny! Hey!
喔
Oh, uh...
丹尼  你认得瑞秋吧  她人很好  长得也不赖  对吧
Danny, you know Rachel. She's nice. She's not bad to look at, right?
谢了  摩妮卡  当然啦
Thanks, Mon. Of course.
你要不要跟她约会  摩妮卡
Do you wanna go out on a date with her? Monica.
好啊  周五可以吗
Absolutely. ls Friday okay?
喔  我的天
Oh, my God.
周五太好了  她都等不及要赴约了
Friday is perfect. She can't wait.
约会时  我可以直接跟她说话吧
On the date, I will be able to talk to her directly, right?
周五见
See you Friday.
你搞什么啊  算了  不用说了
Okay, what the hell was that? You know what? Don't answer me.
我要跟丹尼约会了
I have a date with Danny. Ha!
我怎么会落选
How could I not get the part?
主角就是出身皇后区的  29岁意大利演员
The play was about a 29-year-old Italian actor from Queens.
但是  泰莉雅雪儿突然有空
Well, Talia Shire suddenly became available.
她是欧巴桑
She's a woman!
你要我说什么  人家就是有办法
What can I say? She nailed it.
好吧  还有什么戏份
Uh, okay. ls there anything else?
你一定又会拒绝
Well, you're just gonna say no again, but...
同性恋A片
---gay porn?
佳节快乐
Happy holidays!
圣诞快乐（西班牙文）
[Speak in Spanish]
嗨  圣诞快乐（法文）
And Merry Christmas.
谢谢你  祝你幸福
Oh, thank you, sir. Here's some joy.
菲比  我来看看你做得如何
Hey. How's it going?
很顺利
Well, it's going okay.
那好  我顺便捐点钱  谢谢
Oh, good. Here, let me help you out. Oh, thanks.
不客气
Yeah. Wow. Ha, ha.
新的麂皮外套  好像很贵
Is that a new suede jacket? It looks really expensive.
是的  不便宜
Yeah. I guess.
你刚去做指甲
Just get your nails done?
对  菲比  我只剩这些钱了
Yes, Phoebe, but this is all I have, okay?
谢啦  佳节快乐
Okay, thanks. Happy holidays.
祝你幸福  谢谢
Here's your joy. Thank you.
佳节快乐  等等
Thank you. Happy holidays and-Wait.
只能捐钱  不能拿钱  我跟你换零钱搭公车
You can't take the money out. I'm making change for the bus.
拿零钱就好  其他钱是要救济穷人的
Can't you leave the dollar? This money's for the poor.
我就是穷人  而且还得搭公车
I'm poor. I gotta take the bus.
佳节愉快  可是你不能
Okay. Seasons greetings and everything. But still--
去死  小妞
Bite me, blondie!
除了祝他幸福  我还要
Oh, I'm gonna give him something besides joy. Just--
那个角色根本就是为我而写的  不敢相信我竟然落选
That part was perfect for me. I can't believe I didn't get it.
很遗憾
I'm sorry, man.
你知道该怎么做吗
You know what you should do?
你要自己创造机会
You should make something happen for yourself.
例如  写部电影剧本
You know, like write a play.
就像《心灵捕手》那两个
Write a movie, huh? What about those Good Will Hunting guys?
罗斯  少作白日梦了  就算我写出剧本
Come on, Ross. Be realistic, you know? If I did write something...
哪有办法请到他们来演
...what are the chances I could get those guys to star in it?
有了  我可以自己主演  也可以
Wait a second. I could star in it! Or that.
我不会写剧本  我的意思是  我是演员
I can't write, you know. I mean, I'm an actor.
我没受过编剧的训练  我办不到
I don't have the discipline that it takes, you know. I can't do it.
我可以帮你
I'll help you.
帮你订出时间表  盯着你乖乖照做
Yeah. I'll make up a schedule and make sure you stick to it.
这样我自己也有事做了
Plus it'll give me something to do.
真的  你愿意帮我  对  谢谢
Really? You'd do that for me? Thanks. Yeah.
开始慢慢来  今晚之前
We'll start off slow. The only thing you have to do tonight...
只要想好主角名字
...is come up with the name of your main character.
好了  不能是乔伊
Done. And it can't be Joey.
不是  也不能是约瑟夫
It's not. Or Joseph.
嗨  你怎么啦
Hi. What's up?
我刚看到丹尼跟女生搭地铁
I just saw Danny getting on the subway with a girl...
他还搂着她
...and he had his arm around her.
宝贝  我真为你难过
Oh, honey, I'm sorry.
你的确该难过  一切都要怪你
Well, you should be. This is all your fault.
谁叫你插手我们的感情世界
You meddled in our relationship.
你们根本没在一起
You had no relationship.
不过我已经拟好计划
No, but I was doing my thing, and everything...
一切都按部就班进行中
...was going according to the plan!
拜托  别再提你的鸟计划了
Oh, God. Stop with the plan.
那么  你看到他跟女生在一起
Unh. So what if you saw him with a girl?
又如何  他们不见得是情人
Who cares? That doesn't mean anything.
你就快跟丹尼约会了  到时你可以火力全开  迷得他
You'll go out on a date with Danny and be so charming he'll forget all about...
忘记地铁那个蠢妞
...that stupid subway girl.
那女生的确傻里傻气的
She was kind of stupid.
你说得对  好  我这就去赴约
You're right. All right. I'm just gonna go on the date.
我会去赴约  这就是我的新计划
I'm just gonna go on the date. That is the new plan.
快点  快点
Hurry, hurry!
"多疑" 怎么写  干嘛
Hey, how do you spell "suspicious"? Why?
因为这个角色很 "多疑"
Because I think this character is gonna be suspicious about stuff.
对
Yes!
钱德宾7分  钱德宾0分
Chandler Bing, seven, Chandler Bing, zero.
看你玩那个都快让我抓狂了
You're driving me crazy with that.
好  我不玩就是了  不  继续玩
Okay, I'll stop. No, don't stop.
碗拿远一点  连罗斯都投得进
Move the bowl further away. Ross could make that shot.
真是酷死了  不过你至少进了成人组
Well, you suck. But at least you suck at a man's game now.
要不要玩  我不能跟你玩
You wanna play? I can't be playing games.
罗斯就快回来了  按照他的时间表  我今天应该写完5页
Ross will be home soon. I have to write five pages to stick to his schedule.
你可以先玩30分钟  再继续用功到他回家
Well, so play for the next 30 minutes, then you can write until he gets home.
好吧
All right.
不过  规则应该
But, listen, what do you say we, uh...
更上一层楼
...crank it up a notch?
愿闻其详
I'm intrigued.
要先找到可燃性液体
All right. All we need is a little lighter fluid.
好  不过你小心点  我还想拿回房租订金
Okay, but be careful. I wanna get our security deposit back.
我们发明铁鎚标枪时  就拿不回来了
Yeah, I think we said goodbye to that when we invented hammer darts.
你记得哪面墙壁没补过吗
Do you remember which part of the wall is not spackle?
记得  这里
Uh, yeah, right here.
谢谢  佳节愉快
Thank you. Happy holiday.
小姐  那可是垃圾  不可以
No, that's trash, young lady. No, you can't--
嘿  阻止那位小姐  她竟然捐垃圾
Hey. Stop that young lady! She donated trash!
嘿
Hey.
捐筒着火了
The charity's on fire!
来人啊  太好了  谢谢  我正需要
Help! Good, thank you. I need that.
那是什么鬼东西  现在才早上9点啊
What is this? It's 9:00 in the morning.
我看看“场景  房间
All right. "A room.
一名男子  多疑地走进来”
A man enters. He looks suspicious."
就这样
That's it?
乔伊  你今天应该写5页
Joey, you were supposed to have five pages done by now...
还包括一个高潮
...including an exciting incident.
这是什么垃圾  "大火球游戏规则"
What is all this? "The Official Rulebook of Fireball."
对啊  我们刚在玩这游戏
Yeah, that's the game we played.
很好玩  道具就是一颗网球  一个碗  可燃液体
Yeah, it's great. You take a tennis ball, a bowl and lighter fl--
这对你的事业有帮助吗  我还以为你想当演员
This is helping your career, huh? You wanted to be an actor.
不是发明危险游戏被人告
Not the creator of Crazy Lawsuit Game.
你说得对  我该工作了
You're right, you're right. I'll get back to work.
你真不应该  还带坏他  明知道乔伊应该要工作
And shame on you. You should know better. Joey needs to work.
振作点
Now come on. Hey.
嘿  不行  等你写完5页才还你
No, uh-uh. You can have this back when the five pages are done, huh?
我今晚很开心  我也是
I had a really nice time tonight. So did I.
幸好摩妮卡约我们出来
I'm really glad Monica asked us out.
我很想请你进去  不过我妹来了住我家
I'd love to ask you in but my sister's visiting.
她可能睡在沙发上了  你妹妹
I think she's asleep on the couch. Your sister?
你妹妹睡在沙发上
Your sister's asleep on the couch?
喔  我上次看到你们一起搭地铁  现在她还睡在你沙发上
Ah, I saw you with her on the subway and now she's asleep on the couch.
我就猜是你  太好了  你起床了
Oh, I thought I heard you. Oh, hey, great, you're up.
瑞秋  这是我妹妹克莉丝塔  克莉丝塔  这是瑞秋
Rachel, my sister Krista. Krista, Rachel.
嗨  很高兴认识你
Hi. Nice to meet you.
你应该告诉我要带朋友回来  害我穿得邋里邋遢的
Wish you told me we were having company. I'd have fixed myself.
有差吗  你真恶劣
Like it would help. You are so bad.
是你  是你
You are. You are.
是你  是你  是你  是你
You are. You are. You are. You are!
你完蛋了
You are so dead. Ha.
我要教训你一顿
I'm gonna get you. Aah!
很高兴认识你
Um, it's very nice to meet you.
没有人  没一个人尊重募捐筒
Nobody. Nobody respects the bucket.
大家都丢些莫名其妙的东西
You wouldn't believe what people put in here.
你觉得这像
Look. Okay, does this look like...
垃圾桶吗  不像
...a garbage can to you? No.
像烟灰缸吗  不像
Does it look like an ashtray? No.
像尿桶吗
Does it look like a urinal?
呀哦
Ew!
菲比  你还要回去募捐吗  当然  不过我受够了
So, Pheebs, you gonna go back out there? Yeah, but I'm not gonna take any more crap.
再也不当募捐好好小姐
Okay? No more Mrs. Nice Bucket.
加油  你在街上流浪过  够强悍啊
Yeah, good for you. You're tough. You lived on the street.
我要当回强悍菲比
Yeah, I'm gonna go back to being Street Phoebe.
不过  也不能全当回去
Yeah. Oh, but you know what? I can't go totally back...
因为  强悍菲比才不会鸟你们
...because Street Phoebe really wouldn't be friends with you guys.
嘿
Hey. Hey.
可以问个问题吗  当然
Um, can I ask you guys something? Sure.
我没有兄弟  实在不了解  不过你们会打来打去吗
Urn, I don't have any brothers so I don't know, but did you guys wrestle?
当然会  常常啊
Oh, yeah. All the time.
而且  我从没输过
In fact, I was undefeated.
因为你以前90多公斤
Well, you weighed 200 pounds.
不过我还是跟猫咪一样矫捷
Still, I was quick as a cat.
我昨天遇到丹尼的妹妹
Well, I met Danny's sister yesterday.
就是跟他一起搭地铁的那个  真的假的
Uh, that was the girl on the subway. Oh, you're kidding.
他们非常
And they were very, you know...
会扭打
...wrestle-y.
这样正常吗
But I guess that's normal?
我们现在不会这样了
We don't wrestle now.
我长大变得强壮后就不打了
Not since I got too strong for you. Ha, ha.
长大变壮  对
Too strong for me? Yeah.
你要比划一下吗
You wanna go right now?
我可以立刻打败你  信不信
Because I'll take you right now, buddy. You wanna go?
没问题
Oh, fine.
预备
Ready?
开始
Wrestle!
这个嘛  很好
Okay, you know what, um?
谢谢你们  帮了大忙
Actually, that's great. That helps a lot. Thanks.
赶快走  20分后球赛就要开打了  乔伊  快点
Guys, come on, let's go. The puck drops in 20 minutes. Come on. Joey.
乔伊不能去  我还没写完5页
Joey's not going. I didn't finish my five pages.
明天再写不就成了
Why can't you finish them tomorrow?
因为他明天要修改昨天的5页
Because tomorrow he's redoing yesterday's pages.
我昨天写的有所改进
Yesterday's pages did not reflect my best work.
别再逼他  让他透口气  搞不好会写得更好
Why don't you cut him a little slack? Maybe if he relaxes, he'll get some work done.
他已经透够多气了  这都要感谢你
I think he's been relaxing enough, thanks to you...
跟大火球
...and Fireball.
玩大火球可是很紧张  显然你没玩过
If you think Fireball's relaxing, you obviously have never played.
你拼命压榨乔伊  是因为你太无聊了
The only reason you're doing this to Joey is you're bored.
又不是乔伊害你失业的
It's not his fault that you're unemployed.
我不是失业  只是进修中
I am not unemployed. I'm on sabbatical.
伙计们  你们别吵架
Look, look. Guys, don't fight.
我之所以这么做  是因为我是乔伊的朋友
And the reason I'm doing this is because I am Joey's friend.
如果你也是他好友  就该跟我一样
And if you were a good friend, you'd be doing the same thing.
当好友就得这么混帐
So being a good friend means acting like a jerk?
要是真如你所说  你可真是我第一号好友
If it does, then you're an amazing friend of mine.
别吵了  何不大家玩场大火球  尽弃前嫌
Hey, guys. How about we settle this over a friendly game of Fireball, huh?
我去拆掉防火警铃  何不现在就一了百了
I'll go unhook the smoke detectors. How about we settle this right now?
好了  谁也不准去看球赛
There. Now no one's going to the game. Ha-ha-ha.
门票是我买的  才怪
I paid for those tickets. No, you didn't.
你每次都说要付钱  却一次也没吐过钱  也对
You said you would, but you never did. Oh, yeah.
（中央咖啡厅）
我们终于爬到山顶
So we finally get to the top of the mountain, ahem...
结果这个笨蛋竟然忘了相机
...and airhead here forgets the camera.
我也发生过这种事情
You know, that same thing happened to me one time.
什么时候
When did that happen to you?
记不记得  上次我们不是到公园慢跑  看到那只可爱小鸟
Don't you remember? We were jogging in the park, we saw that pretty bird.
结果想拍  我竟然没带相机
And I wanted to take a picture but I didn't have my camera.
也对  不过追小贩可不算慢跑
Okay. First of all, chasing the churro guy is not jogging.
超好吃  你一定要吃一口
Oh, this is so good. You have got to try it.
真不错
That is good.
糟糕  裤子沾到了  我来擦
Oh, damn. I got it on my pants. Here, I'll get it.
最好上楼换件裤子 否则以后洗不掉
We better take these off or that stain will set.
而且我今晚约会还要穿  喔  真好
I wanna wear these pants on our date tonight. Oh, great.
再见  老天爷啊
Okay, bye. Oh, my God.
不可思议  看吧  我早说过了
That was unbelievable. Okay, see? I told you.
可怜的瑞秋  我不相信他们是兄妹
Yeah, wow. Sorry, Rash. I don't believe they're brother and sister.
他们是兄妹
They're brother and sister?
（非尿桶）
（我没有百货公司简介）
等一下  手张开  让我检查
Wait a minute. Open your hand. Let me take a look.
两毛五  一毛  线头不要
Quarter, dime. Lint? Not interested in that.
这是什么  加拿大硬币  滚蛋
What's this? A Canadian coin? Get out of here!
天啊
Gosh.
不准在募捐筒旁边喝东西
Whoa. No drinks near the bucket.
先放在那边  才准捐款
Set it down over there and then you can make a contribution.
少装一副可怜兮兮的样子
And you can leave the "hurt bunny" look over there too.
嗨  鲍柏  不是叫你滚蛋了吗
Hi, Bob. I thought I told you to get out of here!
菲比  我们接到申诉
Uh, Phoebe, we've been getting complaints.
上面要调你离开
And we're gonna move you to a less high-profile spot.
什么
What?
以后这里由金洁负责  这小妞才没这能耐
Uh, Ginger's gonna take over this corner. That chick can't handle my corner.
你不走  我们就得赶你走
Look, either you leave or we remove you.
好
Fine.
劝你一句  注意那个臭婆娘
All right, I'll give you one pointer. Look out for that bitch.
瑞秋  不是约的7点吗  我看  今天就算了
Oh, hey, Rach. I thought we said 7. Yeah, uh, you know what? Uh, let's skip it.
什么  为什么
What? Uh, why?
你看
Um... Look.
你们兄妹似乎  非常要好
You and your sister seem to have, um, a very special bond--
太好了  又说这句话
Oh, great. That "special bond" again.
我跟我妹感情好  又是哪里让人看不顺眼了
Why do women have such a problem with the fact that I'm close with my sister?
听我说  我不知道事实真相  你有兄弟吗
Okay, look, I don't know, but-Do you have brothers?
没有  我有两个姊姊  其中一个很像男人婆
No, I have two sisters, but one of them actually has a very masculine energy.
你们要好吗  不  她们不是好人
Are you close with them? No, no. They're not very nice people.
好  过来  听着
Okay, come here. Listen.
我真的很喜欢你  交往下去应该会有结果
I really like you, okay? I think this could go somewhere.
我是跟家人感情深厚  你就为了这点拒绝我
So what if I'm close to my family? You gonna let that stand in the way of us?
我也不知道
Well, I-I don't know...
听你这么说也有道理
See, when you put it that way, you know--
丹尼  快点  洗澡水快凉了
Danny, hurry up. The bath's getting cold.
又怎么了  我先走了
What? Yeah, okay, I'll see you later.
路上有小孩在玩耍
Oh, hey. There's some kids playing in the street.
你要不要去叫他们写作业  毁了他们的一天
You wanna go down there, give them a project, ruin their day?
如果你手边有球  就可以插上剃刀
Hey, if they have a ball, maybe you could stick razor blades in it...
教他们玩新游戏  "杀人球"
...and teach them a new game: "Gonna-Need-Stitches Ball."
两位  我整个早上都待在图书馆  已经写完今天的5页了
Hey, guys. I was at the library all morning and I already finished my five pages for today.
那敢情好  我们可以去看昨晚的《骑兵队》比赛了
Great. Now we can go to the Ranger game last night.
不行  门票被罗斯撕掉了
No, dude. Ross tore up the tickets.
没有让你分心的事情  就比较容易专心吧
I guess when you don't have so many distractions, it's easier for you to focus, huh?
没人整天跟在你屁股后面  也比较得心应手吧
Yeah, or also when you don't have somebody breathing down your neck all the livelong day!
随便你们说  总之我写完了  而且写得还不错
Well, that's fine, but the important thing is I finished it. And I think it's really good.
不过你们帮忙念台词  才是真正帮大忙  可不可以帮我这个忙
But you know what would help me, is if I could hear it. Would you guys read it for me?
好吧  好
Yeah, all right. All right.
好  "一间普通的纽约公寓
Okay. "It's a typical New York City apartment.
两个男人正在家里" 罗斯
Two guys are hanging out." Ross?
嗨  老兄  有什么事
"Hey, man." "What is up?"
"昨天  是我错了  对不起"
"About yesterday. I was really wrong. I am sorry."
"是我  我才该道歉  我反应过头了"
"No, it was me. I'm sorry. I overreacted."
或许我们都有错  反正我们都是为了朋友
"Maybe it was both of us. But we had our best friend's inter--
我们都是为了朋友好"
But we had our best friend's interest at heart."
"我非常不好意思"
"Could I be more sorry?"
"我不知道  我才是该道歉的
"I don't know. I am one sorry...
古生物学家
...polontologist."
乔伊  我们懂了
All right, Joey, we get it.
对不起  我也该道歉
I'm sorry. I'm sorry too.
不  你们要继续读下去  精彩的才要上场  继续念
Oh, no, no, no. Keep reading. The good part's coming up. Keep going.
"对不起  钱德"
"I am sorry, Chandler."
"对不起  罗斯"
"I am sorry, Ross."
帅哥上场
Ahem. "A handsome man enters."
"你们好吗"
"Hey. How's it going, guys?
不知道你们在扯什么  不过我要向你们两位道谢
I don't know what you two are talking about, but I'd just like to say thanks to both of you.
你让我不放弃自己
You. You wouldn't let me give up on myself.
你  你与我一起创造了大火球
And you. Well, you co-created Fireball.
剧终
The End." Yeah.
这就花了你一整天
This took you all day?
没有  我只写了5分钟
No, no, this only took five minutes.
其他时间都在写  终极大火球游戏规则
I spent the rest of the day coming up with New Ultimate Fireball. Ha, ha!
场景在一般纽约公寓
Okay. "it's a typical New York apartment.
屋内有两个女生
Two girls are just hanging out." Go.
嗨  凯莉  你好吗  我很好
"Hi, how are you doing, Kelly?" "I'm doing just fine.
天啊  提芬妮  你今天好香
God, Tiffany, you smell so great."
我喷了新香水
"it's my new perfume.
你靠近一点才闻得仔细
Why don't you come closer where you can really appreciate it?"
乔伊  你这大变态  恶心死了
Oh, you know, Joey, you are sick. This is disgusting.
我才不要念呢
I'm not reading this.
什么  等等  帅哥才刚要上场呢
What? Wait, wait, wait. The handsome man was about to enter!